Ever wish your boss was dead?
Horrible Bosses is a comedy, crime film directed by Seth Gordon.
For Nick, Kurt and Dale, the only thing that would make the daily grind more
tolerable would be to grind their intolerable bosses into dust.
Quitting is not an option, so, with the benefit of a few-too-many drinks and some dubious advice from a hustling ex-con, the
three friends devise a convoluted and seemingly foolproof plan to rid themselves of their respective employers...
permanently.
Nick Hendricks, played by Jason Bateman.
Dale Arbus, played by Charlie Day.
Kurt Buckman, played by Jason Sudeikis.
Dave Harken, played by Kevin Spacey.
Julia Harris, played by Jennifer Aniston.
Bobby Pellitt, played by Colin Farrell.
Horrible Bosses is a 2011 American crime comedy film directed by Seth Gordon and written by Michael
Markowitz, John Francis Daley, and Jonathan Goldstein, from a story by Markowitz.
It stars Jason Bateman, Charlie Day, Jason Sudeikis, Jennifer Aniston, Colin
Farrell, Kevin Spacey, Donald Sutherland, and Jamie Foxx.
The plot follows three friends, played by Bateman, Day, and Sudeikis, who decide to murder their
respective overbearing, abusive bosses, portrayed by Spacey, Aniston, and Farrell.
Markowitz's script was bought by New Line Cinema in 2005 and the film spent six years in various
states of pre-production, with a variety of actors attached to different roles.
By 2010, Goldstein and Daley had rewritten the script,
and the film finally went into production.
The film premiered at Grauman's Chinese Theatre on June 30, 2011,
and was released on July 8, 2011, by Warner Bros.
The film received mixed reviews and grossed $209.8 million worldwide.
A sequel, Horrible Bosses 2, was released on November 26, 2014.
The film explores themes of bad boss, employee, death of
father, stakeout, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted.